## Thomas J Lazore

## Full Stack Developer

Software developer currently attending Georgia Tech's Full Stack Coding Boot Camp. Working with technologies such as JavaScript, Express, and Node for development of group and solo projects. Past relevant experience interning as a research assistant while developing the front end of a project for Rochester Institute of Technology. A leadership background as a paramedic has developed skills to be an effective and resourceful team member as well as independent worker.



# Work History

2021-07 -

Current

#### Address

Savannah, GA, 31410

#### **Phone**

315-778-6632

#### E-mail

tomlazore@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tlaze



Javascript	•••○○	2017-09 -
Bootstrap	••••	2020-03
MySQL	•••○○	
Node	••••	
Express	••••	
Python	•••○○	
Java	••000	
JQuery	••••	
HTML	••••	

#### Server

Six Pence Pub, Savannah, GA

- Displayed enthusiasm and promoted excellent service to customers, successfully increasing referrals and walk-in business.
- Maintained thorough menu knowledge to sufficiently answer questions regarding menu item sourcing, ingredients and cooking methods.
- Replenished food items, paper products and canned goods to keep pantry well-stocked during busy periods.
- Increased sales significantly by upselling higher-end products to customers

#### **Paramedic**

Irondequoit Ambulance, Irondequoit, NY

- Developed and maintained rapport with coworkers and local hospital staff to facilitate efficient patient care.
- Identified appropriate medications based on potential interactions with other medicines, accurately calculating correct dosages according to drugs on hand and patient's weight.
- Worked en-route to hospital to prepare patients for arrival or surgery and control wounds.
- Delegated life-saving tasks to provide comprehensive treatment to triaged patients in emergency situations.

CSS	••••
Git	•••○○
Heroku	••••
SQL integration	••••
Testing and bugging	••••
Software	

Development

2019-06 -	Research As
2019-08	Rochester Institu
	<ul> <li>Prepared mo</li> </ul>
	and foundati
	<ul> <li>Presented te</li> </ul>
	audiences th

## sistant

ute Of Technology, Rochester, NY

- aterials for submission to agencies tions to fund research.
- chnical research results to diverse nrough written, visual and oral media.
- Supported research and development efforts to create new products, equipment and processes.
- Researched and interpreted large volumes of scientific data and literature.



## **Certifications**

20212	Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp
2021-05	NASM Certified Personal Trainer
2015-07	Paramedic
2012-05	Emergency Medical Technician
2012-09	Firefighter 1



## **Education**

2018-09 -No Degree: Computer Science

2019-09 Monroe Community College - Rochester, NY

> • Relevant Coursework Completed: Intro to Computer Science & Python

2011-09 -**Associate of Applied Science: Fire** 20122 **Protection Technology** 

Monroe Community College - Rochester, NY



Never Alone | https://github.com/tlaze/NeverAlone | https://never-alone-platform.herokuapp.com/

**Description:** Team of 4 members developing a social media application geared towards mental health. User's can post their thoughts and how they feel. While signing up users are greeted with a welcome email thanking them and informing them of the apps mission statement.

**Responsibilities:** Creation, editing, and deletion of posts | Making the application mobile responsive.

#### **Technology Used:**

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Javascript | Node | Express | Ha ndlebars | Express-Session | MySQL2 | Sequelize | Connect-Session-Sequelize | Heroku | Nodemailer

Tech Blog | https://github.com/tlaze/tech-blog | https://cryptic-thicket-49114.herokuapp.com/

**Description:** Forum based application for creating posts and adding comments. The homepage displays all the posts and comments users have made. Logged in users can view their dashboard containing all the posts they created. They also have the option to create, update, or delete their posts. After being inactive for a while users are logged out.

#### **Technology Used:**

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Javascript | Node | Express | Ha ndlebars | Express-Session | MySQL2 | Sequelize | Connect-Session-Sequelize | Heroku

Weather Dashboard | https://github.com/tlaze /weather-dashboard | https://tlaze.github.io /weather-dashboard/

**Description:** Fetches data from OpenWeather API to display current and future weather conditions for

cities that users enter. Previous searches are saved even after users refresh or leave the page.

### Technology Used:

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Javascript | JQuery | OpenWe atherOneAPI